{
    "subject": "Paul_Scheer",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "June_Diane_Raphael",
    "human_readable": "Paul Scheer is married to June Diane Raphael.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885388016700745,
            "question": "Is June Diane Raphael married to Paul Scheer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9743052124977112,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9469465017318726,
            "question": "To whom is Paul Scheer married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9384036660194397,
            "question": "Who is Paul Scheer married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9333365559577942,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9120078682899475,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Paul Scheer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999391198158264,
            "question": "Who are Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8920358419418335,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the couple, Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7871730327606201,
            "question": "What is the name of Paul Scheer's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6089052557945251,
            "question": "Are Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael known for their work in entertainment?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Scheer is married to June Diane Raphael.",
            "html": "yago_8137_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Paul Scheer's wife?",
            "html": "yago_8137_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the couple, Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?",
            "html": "yago_8137_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?",
            "html": "yago_8137_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8137_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that June Diane Raphael and Paul Scheer are married, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}